Del: Let's go!
Iden: Del, get us outta here!
Del: I'm on it!
Hask: Admiral Versio.
Hask: Agent Hask, reporting. Mission accomplished, sir.
Garrick: Congratulations, Commander Hask.
Iden: So, we’re not completely alone. Some of the crew stayed with us. Protected the refugees against those who wouldn't.
Del: How are they?
Iden: Shaken. Confused. But safe.
Iden: Just want to know what's next.
Del: We have to warn people.
Iden: Who? The Rebels? They're just going to toss us in Sunspot Prison before we can even say a word.
Del: That’s why I think you should just take the **Corvus** and go. Leave me a TIE fighter. I’ll set off a distress call, wait for the Rebels to find me.
Iden: You really think I'm gonna let you just float out here alone?
Iden: Del. We're Inferno Squad. You and me.